# Leya Salazar Romero

Graphic Designer & Web Designer



leyasalazar.com leyasalazarromero@gmail.com 8622878979

# **Profile**

Creative and meticulous graphic designer and web designer graduated with the Web Design and Front-End Development A.A.S. degree and Graphic Design Certificate from Minneapolis College. Experience designing functional, aesthetically pleasing and inspiring works with a background in photography, mural art and digital art.

# **Experience**

#### Freelance Graphic Designer - Illustrator, July, 2021 - Present

- Create designs and digital content
- T-shirts, decals and stickers production

#### Content Creator, @soyperuana.pe, November, 2021 - Present

- Design one weekly post for the instagram account with more than 15k followers.
- · Work within established brand identity guidelines

# Front-End Developer, MPLS Design Show, 2021

- Work with peers to create a website in order to promote the work of graduating students
- Primarily use bootstrap programming language
- Utilize effective teamwork and communication skills in order to be a contributing teammate

http://www.mplscollegedesignshow.com/

# Web Designer and Front-End Developer, MPLS Apparel Portfolio, 2021

- Utilize the MS Teams platform to communicate with peers to build a website highlighting apparel graduating students
- Utilize bootstrap programming language to create the website
- Collaborate with moodboard ideas and designing concepts https://mcappareltechnologies.com

#### **Education**

#### Minneapolis College

Minneapolis, MN 2018 - 2021

Associate of Applied Science Web Design and Front-End Development

Certificate, 30 Credits

Graphic Design: Print and Digital Media

# **Lens School of Visual Arts**

Madrid, Spain 2013-2014

Intermediate 2 Certificate Photography

#### **Adittional Information:**

Minneapolis College Alumni Exhibit 2 Hennepin Theatre Trust Present - March, 2022

Participation with five projects in the exhibition. https://hennepintheatretrust.org/events/minneapolis-college-alumni-exhibit-2/

#### **Skills**

- Adobe Creative Cloud (Illustrator, Xd, InDesign, Photoshop, Lightroom)
- Color & Pattern
- Print Production
- Illustration
- HTML, CSS, JQuery, JavaScript
- Visual Studio Code, Figma
- Customer Service
- Adaptability
- Collaboration
- Problem-solving
- · Languages: Spanish, English

